This is the hero of this story, which begins a few years ago in Coimbatore.
Our father will be a hero to all children, just like their
father.  But to me,
my father is a superhero.  He is a college
professor.
Are you wondering why Bud doesn't come to school?  Just to
see us.  Before I say [music],
I
introduce everyone else.
This is our mother [music]
Sweet, happy, innocent. Our
mother is also a college professor.  Oh, my
father and mother [music] are having a romance at home, I'm so sorry, please
watch it.
[Music]
Such a love, even at this age.
This is my brother, Boxer [Music]. No matter what problem I have,
he will always come knocking and
asking.  Then, if you ask me why he was added to boxing, he's
already fighting with everyone who comes to him
.  Why is he now fighting
all this boxing? He's been
fighting with the Sports Gives Discipline for a long time
.  He is going to fight for victory from now on
.  I tore it.
[Music] Let's
beat everyone.  He
will beat me too.  But if someone
hits me, I'll hit them terribly.  [Music]
This character has been hanging around with us for a long time, you might be
wondering who he is.  My life friend Jeeva.   He
steals and eats biscuits, and he
drinks juice that my brother stole.  [Music]
Then my brother chases me and beats me until I get beaten
.  When
my father went to school, he would carry his bag [of music] on his head and
walk to the bus stop.  This is all Ivan Abinga.   It would be a
great pleasure if we were alone
.  But we only joined in on one thing [music]
.
Hello,
hello, father,
how are you?   I
'm fine, Father.  Hello,
teacher,
this is the father.
Hello,
welcome, how are you?
What the hell are you doing, like making a new wish?  It's
normal for parents like us to call you like this,
right? We bought the book from the store you mentioned
.  We bought the uniform at the store you mentioned
.  I don't
know what else I missed.   It's not that it's much more
important.  What are you doing with the cows,
why are you doing this? What's the problem today?
Manisha
S. Manisha was our biggest
enemy when we were young.  It's her hobby to get stuck in the mess whenever she sees us
.
[Screaming]
You know he is the whole school, you don't
understand, father, is it your problem that these people speak Tamil?
Yes, you should not speak Tamil.
This school is in this school. [Music] If they don't speak
Tamil in Tamil Nadu, then
they will go to Pakistan and speak. This is an English medium school. If it is English medium, there is no
English education.
Father, education in English is that much. If there is
no way for Tamil, then how can Father defend English?
[Laughter]
Who said that Father, these people are future-oriented,
not relying on English, they are relying on their knowledge.
English is just a language.
Father, it is a tool. [Music] Look, communication
is Tamil. That is our identity. Father, a
person who has forgotten his identity. He has forgotten the
land where he was born, the
town where he grew up, his own country, and
an identity for himself.  He
went to another country for something he wanted and became a slave to someone there. He was a
little bit spoiled and
spoiled. In the end, he misunderstood that this was his
identity and not only did he but also
his descendants
live as slaves. [Music] That's what happened. Father. Father.
Our lineage that ruled this world is a ten thousand year old language.
[Music] A language with grammar. Why is
Tamil the oldest language in the world? I'm not saying that you
shouldn't teach English,
but you're saying that you shouldn't speak Tamil.
That's what I'm saying.
Father, please, Father, why don't you call me mommy? You called me mommy. Mother is Tamil. Is that your mother tongue?
[Applause] Even though
we all speak English, we are
Tamilians.
[Music]
[Music] I
told you that right then. No, our
father is a superhero.
You're probably asking what the principal said. [Music] My father is getting tense.  We can
talk about whatever we want, right?  But we should never talk negatively about Tamil
.  Oh [music] I didn't even bring
my father to get the report card
.
Do you know why I came here to collect taxes for this problem?
Sketch [Music] Not for my father, but for the
principal's father.
Father, mother,
the farewell party is over, and
school will end in four more days.
Besides, the public exam is
tomorrow, and the last tuition class is tomorrow.
Go talk to her, be respectful.   Can
we talk, Jeeva? I'm scared.
Then give me a letter.
Hey,
that's not for us,
but [music] He came and sat next to me, did he know that I would
come and sit here? He
came and sat here, excuse me,
sir
[music]
Dude, is someone new? Hey, hey, hey, hey,
first,
I saw this girl for the first time.
I've been making love, thinking I'll be the first to fall in
love.   Did you push it away
?  Sit down,
you won't be okay.
Now,
sir, make me some coffee.
How are you,
dear?
Help me.  Hey, I'll buy you some
time,
so
excuse me, hey, she
said she's taking a new course, why are you so angry? Tell me,
you're the one who got the jalebi, tell me, new
admission, no, no,
morning patch,
this is it, [music]
is gone, look,
who is this for?
It depends on your reaction.
Okay okay
okay
[Music]
Nalakka,
tell me, brother, don't you feel like saying, "I don't
play well?" I don't
know who I am. I am the class leader of the
Standard A section of the class.
Manisha [
Music]
You don't like shirts at all. I am a man  Will you do it
?   I
will do these things.
Okay, boss, lift the bicycle.
Hey, let's ride a bicycle.
Hey Pastor, please tell me.
You're crazy, my dear
.  I'll take the bicycle.  No
problem.
Hey brother, why did you give my man a letter
?  Who is your man?
[Laughter]
My man, he's like someone who gives a letter to someone and then rips it up without buying it.
Hey, if you say it's Manisha,
she's the one who bought it and wrote the
letter,
I'll say it's Manisha.  Why
are you saying everything in a roundabout way?
Tell me directly.   Don't say it directly
.  [Laughter]
Hey, why are you putting your hands on my friend?
I'll lay my hands on you, okay?  Are you arrogant and arrogant, like you
have a piece of paper to rub on
?  I will also go and gather people
.
Good girl, drink.
Brother,
this Balaji must have been walking down the dead end of the main street on the same day.  The wedding is a mess.   Let's
see, Lusa. Hello, hello
Four children
are in my room
[Music]
Hey, who is this?
Who is this guy? [Laughter] The
problem is that
everyone in the department will
say, "What's wrong?"
Which department? [Music] Mechanical
department I have a lot of people in the
mechanical department. Mac Tiger Mac
Lion Mac Elephant Mac Donald
and Another Mac Lion Max, did you
beat me?
Brother, I
beat you like this, like this.
[Screaming]
[Music]
Hey, chase and chase
Just put on your mask and leave it alone, just
walk like that, mother,
tell me, mother, it's
not possible
[Music]
[Music] Let's go to the
city, a big
building, high-tech infrastructure, a
30-40 bus, if you've seen all this, you're
right, it's an engineering college, as you think
.  This is not
just in Coimbatore, it is all over India
.  For what kind of people is the fee for playing [music]
small or large?
Well, every department in this engineering college has its own unique
character.  I should have read All Boys No
Girls Get Mechanics
or All Girls No Boys [Music]
Beautiful Biotech
.  But I studied
psychology, and
this is the most difficult department in engineering.
You can even go shirtless.  But you
absolutely cannot go without an ID card.  Don't assume that everyone
is studying engineering, just that
engineering kids are normal
.  Four years [Music] Eight
semesters 64 papers One project
Internship 10 15 lab m1 m2 m3
Fluid [Music] Mechanics Solid
Mechanics DSP
I didn't say this DSP.  This
DSP degree stopping paper, I
studied hard and passed all these,
internal and external,
got the record note sign,
finally I passed all the exams in one exam and got the
placement, I will fall at your feet,
then you will do one thing
[Music]
Hello sir.
Good mark,
thank you sir.
Good percentage but no job.
Yes, sir.
400,000 people come out in one year
.  How
can you give work to everyone?
Then why don't you ask
the students if they are going to engineering college and fail?
Look at the parents and
ask.  Okay, let's come to our college.   We
got the same college, the same department, the same class, the same bench, but we didn't get the
same room in the hostel.
Next up are our college seniors.  This is
Gethu Senior.  This is a
senior who is struggling.  This is a senior member of the Ketty Panchayat.
This is a senior member of the Kattam Panchayat.  Sir, my
dear brother.
Hey, come here, senior, you're all dressed up,
okay, go, let's go,
brother, Sudhakaran, brother, brother, okay, okay, you
go, you go, Sudhakaran,
brother, we don't
know who, brother,
buy it, give it, give it to me, what's up, hey Sudhakaran,
my brother, go, I'm washing it, why are you
doing this, hey,
what's up,
first year, my friend, who are you, brother,
Sudhakaran, brother, okay, go, go,
oh Sudhakaran, brother, if there is anyone, let's try and
see, Sudhakaran,
brother, don't go
Sudhakaran, what's wrong with you, brother? What's wrong with you
now?
I'm going to destroy you.
Darling.
Hey little boy, are you a volunteer or a
first-year student who is coming and staring?
Oh, what's the point of that?
Okay, let's go.
Hey, the one who sang the song is the only one who is worthy.   We need
to develop contact.  We need
to develop influence.
Who do you know?
Do you know Sudhakaran brother?
Do you know Sudhakaran's brother?   I
know.
He is my brother.
Okay, let's go.   Don't
go, it
hurts,
you're the one who gave me your mouth and got hit.
Now both of you are coming to apologize. You
should have told me about him then, don't go.   You're
talking all the time,
okay, what are you going to do now?
Yes, what are you going to do now?
Buy some biryani and eat it.
Here, everyone eats the same
meal.  They will cook biryani for you only, they will cook it for you.
Tomorrow is our department
function. Tomorrow, our department
will cook biryani for everyone.  They won't let us do it then
.
Why?
Because you are in a different department.  [Music]
What kind of biryani do you get?   If
you give a coupon, you get biryani.
I don't have it.
Who is there?   I ca
n't say.  It is with Vishnu.
Hallelujah,
brother.
Sarita is my brother.  The biryani is all
burnt.
Buy biryani curd rice.  Kar, machan, kar, you
are asking me to eat. Where are you?
Eat kar, eat biryani. [Music]
Eat
[Music]
What did you make?
There is no biryani, machan.  Look here, the guard is
a little girl, they are asking
us to eat all this. Look
here, I have brought all the bags for biryani. Instinct, Instinct College. You are from which college? Which department is this? Biotech. Biotech lawyer. He doesn't lie. He invented. He invented. Let's go. Hey, what's here? Let's eat and go to
Five Start next door. Hey, come on.
I'll come. You go. Manisha,
take the bag. What's the use of us? So,
[Music]
Tell our warden about this Vishnu and Sanjay. Somehow,
send both of them out of the room. Convince the warden that you and I are in the same room. Let's both of us
settle down together.
Alleluia. [Music] Alleluia. Alleluia. Alleluia. Alleluia. Alleluia. Alleluia. Alleluia.
[Music]
Hey, hey, hey,
I'm  I want to ask you something,
who is that?
Listen,
no, I don't know how you're going
to take it.
Listen,
no, no, this is different. [Music]
Where did you get this biryani?
No, I've been looking for a long time. The biryani is
burnt.  How did you
get this?  [Music]
I'm on the second counter.
Second counter, second counter, I
just missed it. Actually, I'll go and
look.
Uncle, there's biryani at the second counter
.  I
remember that as long as you are here, love will never have any problems.
I've seen you somewhere.  I've been watching you both
.  I won't say anything. Do
we all remember the same tuition?
What do you remember?
I [music] am the moon.   Is Khadi Khadi
?   Is
Adi Adi
?
Which department are you in?  [Music]
Oh, this department?
No way.   Please come
often from now on.
[Music]
Hey brother [Music] Come on, talk okay okay Where are you going,
brother? Come on, come on, come on,
come on [
Music]
Hey, what are you doing here,
brother? We came to see you, brother, this
morning. [Clears throat]
Look in the room. [Laughs] We
forgot to say good morning. Did you forget to say good morning? Much much, hi,
Nila, good morning, good morning,
look.
[Music] No, I don't care. I'm hot. Hey, this is not good. Hey, brother, come and clean me now. Okay, it's been 35 days, so I'm not hot. [Music]
Okay, Sanjay, hi,
weekend, please come, please come, please come, please come, please come. [Music] Manisha, I'm not here for my birthday, please, please, please, please.  [Laughter]
Hi Nila,
hi,
I want to meet friends.
I don't have any friends
except us.
Okay, boy. Then this is it.
[Music] Then this is it.
[Screaming] It's
me. [Music]
Then this is it. I have to
explain everything.
Then
[music]
Hey, then,
then, I'm talking to you, Dad.
Dad,
what's the phone waiting? You
won't call me either.
Dad, no, Dad, you're
vacating the house
. Come here this weekend. I'll send you the address of the new house.
[Music]
Hey brother,
what's up?
I'm moving my instrument home,
that's all we brought here
.
I thought I only knew the super lesson.  Please put on some music.
This is our
interest, even if you don't talk to us.
We study engineering just because they tell us at home.
Super, you'll be performing at the hostel function next month
.
Hey, come here now, I do
n't want to be in the hostel, I
don't want to be in the hostel.
Hey, why is
this biotech department
going to have this biotech function?   Thank you, Wright
.
Uncle,
uncle, don't worry, if everything you say is
true, I know. Can we go and
talk?
Hey, don't talk like a fool, Kottamedu
Kumaran. I know someone who can
hang him.
What are we going to do with Mr. Kumara
?  Let's go to our legal office.
Should we file a lawsuit asking for a place to go?
Just tell your gardener to do it and I'll give you
alms.
Hey,
stay here, boy.  I myself am a love failure
.   I
understand, brother. No matter what you want to say,
I'll finish what I say.
[Music]
Hello,
say hello, madams. Listen
to what I'm saying. I listened.
I didn't listen then
. I listened when you said it.  Why
ask now?   The seniors are the only ones who say, "Hey,
Anna, Anna, this guy is the
only one who has been kind to
my friend since he was a child, isn't that
just the two of you, or is there something else?"
Adi, you must be talking nonsense.
Already, my sister's absence is causing a big problem at home
.
Adi, please understand.
I understand.  I understand.
I understand well.
I understand who you are.  Do you know who you are?
[Music]
Hey,
what's up? Suddenly, I gave you a piece of cake without even putting it on.
[Music]
No, no, Adi, I've been drinking. Is that the
cake I told you about today?  [Music] It's a serious
viral infection, so we can cut that time and
burn it.
A big doctor, go to the bathroom,
hey [music], why don't you leave it? Then we can
wash ourselves in the bathroom. Swaha
Love Peyaliyar Aravas
don't need all the luggage, even four friends
are enough.  There just isn't enough time to make love
.
Everything remains, including phone balance and pocket money.  Oh, I'll
go home for the weekend.
I will also clean my friends' clothes.  I will call my
parents regularly.  We did a lot of music, including participating in external
college competitions, composing
songs and uploading them on YouTube, and setting up a
Facebook page for Hip Hop Tamil
.
Please check if the record is submitted correctly.  Since Sudhakaranna was not there,
Mottai and Dan started
dancing around, saying that they were the next to go
.
They will cause trouble wherever they see it.  A year has
passed just like that.  We finished the second year [music] and moved on to the
third year.
Hey, don't worry, this is a book by Paul Ather.
What's so ugly about the mat? Brother,
just India,
your brother, this college?
Otherwise, will you buy me a seat?
What is that?
Oh my God, why not?
Hey, your brother is drinking that donut in the canteen
.  [Music]
Hey, my brother, no
one knows about this college.
Egg Manisha,
when I think about it, I should go and
take care of my brother.   I
believe in saving [music]
[screaming] Sing, sing, sing, sing, I do
n't know how to
sing, I don't know how to sing, hey
sing, oh my god, the
golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the golden sugar, the
golden sugar, the golden sugar, how is it so good, it's  He
came, raised his
head, ran away, scared, hey,
you're wearing sandals, hey
Oh [music] Tie it up
.
Now don't tie it up, tie it up
[music]
Hey senior, did you tie it up
Hey [music] Will
you sit down, sit down, sit down, you sit down.
What's your problem with these foxes? Don't you have any control
over the seniors?
This guy is nothing like you.
Leave Freya alone. I'll take care of him.   What
you say is correct, brother.
You're the senior in college, you see.   Leave it alone,
I'll watch.   He's
trying something.  Come on,
brother, come here,
what's the problem between you and them?
I'm not here. They've been doing this since they were little
.
I'm also watching.  These people should
not be left alone.  I'm
waiting for you to tell me not to let you go.
Hey, you're a hairy man, this area is a panjabi, hey, you're a
soso, [Music]
[Music]
What happened, wait a minute,
father,
father, if you don't know, you'll
fall, then you'll
know, come and see
[Music]
Brother, brother, I
trusted you too, I
bought you a biryani, biryani, you're hiding like this, you'll just hide like this, you'll end up like this, what a
brother, you're not there, you're a hairy man, what a brother, you're not there, you're a hairy man, what a brother, you're not there, you're a hairy man, what a brother, you're not there, you're a hairy man, what a brother,
you're a hairy man